{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which team has won the most World Cups?",
      "options": ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Germany", "Uruguay"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the top scorer in Bundesliga history?",
      "options": [
        "Klaus Fischer",
        "Robert Lewandowski",
        "Jupp Heynckes",
        "Gerd Müller"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which goalkeepers have kept the most Champions League clean sheets?",
      "options": ["Iker Casillas", "Manuel Neuer", "Gianluigi Buffon", "Dida"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the only player to win champions league with 3 different clubs?",
      "options": [
        "Thiago Alcantara",
        "Samuel Eto’o",
        "Clarence Seedorf",
        "Marcel Desailly"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which player has scored the most hat-tricks?",
      "options": [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Ali Daei",
        "Sunil Chhetri"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "In football, what is the Puskás Award given for?",
      "options": [
        "Best save made",
        "Best goal scored",
        "Most goals scored",
        "Most clean sheets"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country won the first-ever FIFA World Cup in 1930?",
      "options": ["Brazil", "West Germany", "Paraguay", "Uruguay"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the youngest player to have ever scored a goal in the English Premier League?",
      "options": [
        "James Milner",
        "Cesc Fabregas",
        "James Vaughan",
        "Mikael Forssell"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "How many UEFA Champions League titles have Real Madrid won",
      "options": ["11", "12", "13", "14"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the oldest player to have ever played in a FIFA World Cup match?",
      "options": [
        "Ángel Labruna",
        "Ali Boumnijel",
        "Faryd Mondragón",
        "Essam El-Hadary"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which team holds the record for the most consecutive wins in a single English Premier League season?",
      "options": ["Manchester United", "Chelsea", "Manchester City", "Arsenal"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the all-time leading goalscorer in the history of the Spanish La Liga?",
      "options": [
        "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "Lionel Messi",
        "Telmo Zarra",
        "Alfredo Di Stéfano"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Italian football club holds the record for the most Serie A titles won?",
      "options": ["AC Milan", "Inter Milan", "Juventus", "Napoli"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "In which year was the first UEFA European Championship held?",
      "options": ["1952", "1956", "1960", "1964"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which club has won the most consecutive Ligue 1 titles?",
      "options": [
        "Paris Saint-Germain",
        "AS Saint-Étienne",
        "Lille OSC",
        "Olympique Lyonnais"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
